hartstrings.com 2015-06-07

# Privacy Policy | Hartstrings

Your privacy on the internet is important to us at Hartstrings.com. Our online privacy policy describes the types of information we gather online and how we use it. Please read this information carefully. If the online information practices at Hartstrings.com change we will let you know by posting the Privacy Policy adjustments on our Website.

Use of Information:

We gather certain types of customer information in an effort to improve your shopping experience and to communicate with you about our products, services, promotions and contests. Hartstrings.com collects two types of information about users: “Personal Information” (such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information and the items you have purchased) and “Aggregate Information” (such as information about how many users log on to our sites on a daily basis).

Personal Information:

Personal Information is collected on line when users voluntarily register with Hartstrings.com to purchase items, receive electronic mailers, use community and communication services, answer surveys and enter contests and other promotional opportunities provided on Hartstrings.com. In addition, we also collect information when users make a purchase, and when users utilized the “email to a Friend” feature. We also maintain a record of your product interests and purchases online. We may receive personal usage and demographic information from third parties we work with to monitor trends and purchasing habits.

Aggregate Information:

Aggregate information is non-personally identifiable/anonymous information about you such as age, gender, types of products purchased, pages you access most frequently or search terms you enter. Aggregate information is used in a collective manner and no single personal can be identified by that complied information.

Children and Privacy:

Hartstrings.com is concerned about the safety of children when they use the internet and understands that children may not understand all the provisions of our Privacy Policy or make informed decisions about the choices that are made available to adult users of the Hartstrings.com website. In accordance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent.

How to Contact Us:

Hartstrings customer service department is here to help you with any of your questions or concerns.  We are available Monday – Friday 8:30 am – 5 pm EST

Feel free to contact us via any of the information listed below:

  * **PHONE** :  Toll Free Number: 888-535-0030
  * **EMAIL** :  [csserv@hartstrings.com](mailto:csserv@hartstrings.com "Email csserv@hartstrings.com")
  * **MAIL:**   Hartstrings Customer Service   680 American Avenue Suite 101 King of Prussia, PA 19406
